<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes Documentation</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/</link><description>Recent content in Home on hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/about/</guid><description>This project is built to make working with bootstrap components much easier in hugo. It aims to be simple, while providing many powerful features.
About the author GitHub Mail Project links Source Code Documentation Issues Dependencies Hugo (License: Apache-2.0) Bootstrap as well as Bootstrap icons (License: MIT) The theme and its documentation are licensed under the GNU Lesser General Public License version 3.0 or later. The terms and conditions of the GNU General Public License version 3.</description></item><item><title>Alerts</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/alert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/alert/</guid><description>A small and colored box to embed into your site to attract the users attention</description></item><item><title>Apache License 2.0</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/apache-2.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/apache-2.0/</guid><description>Apache License Version 2.0, January 2004
http://www.apache.org/licenses/
TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION
1. Definitions. &amp;quot;License&amp;quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.
&amp;quot;Licensor&amp;quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.
&amp;quot;Legal Entity&amp;quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity.</description></item><item><title>Bootstrap MIT License</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/bootstrap-mit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/bootstrap-mit/</guid><description>The MIT License (MIT) Copyright (c) 2011-2022 Twitter, Inc.
Copyright (c) 2011-2022 The Bootstrap Authors
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description></item><item><title>Carousel</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/carousel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/carousel/</guid><description>A slideshow of pictures: Displays multiple pictures in one place</description></item><item><title>Customize bootstrap</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/customize/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/customize/</guid><description>Customization Table of contents CSS customization Example This site&amp;rsquo;s bootstrap customizations Shortcode Customization CSS customization To customize the bootstrap Sass Variables, create the file assets/sass/bootstrap.scss. Here you can add all the customization features for the bootstrap CSS. The other bootstrap files are available in the bootstrap/ namespace.
Your can change the bootstrap variables to customize how bootstrap looks and feels. For more information about customizing bootstrap, please refer to the Bootstrap Documentation.</description></item><item><title>GNU General Public License version 3.0</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/gpl-3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/gpl-3.0/</guid><description>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007
Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. https://fsf.org/
Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
Preamble The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works.
The licenses for most software and other practical works are designed to take away your freedom to share and change the works.</description></item><item><title>GNU Lesser General Public License version 3.0</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/lgpl-3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/licenses/lgpl-3.0/</guid><description>GNU LESSER GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007
Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. https://fsf.org/
Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
This version of the GNU Lesser General Public License incorporates the terms and conditions of version 3 of the GNU General Public License, supplemented by the additional permissions listed below.
0. Additional Definitions. As used herein, &amp;ldquo;this License&amp;rdquo; refers to version 3 of the GNU Lesser General Public License, and the &amp;ldquo;GNU GPL&amp;rdquo; refers to version 3 of the GNU General Public License.</description></item><item><title>Icons</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/icon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/icon/</guid><description>Embed icons into your text/elements</description></item><item><title>Inject the bootstrap styles</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/inject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/inject/</guid><description>Injection To import the stylesheets, javascript and fonts (used for the bootstrap icons), just include the partial bootstrap.html into your header:
&amp;lt;head&amp;gt; ... {{- partial &amp;#34;bootstrap.html&amp;#34; }} ... &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; It is important, that the partial bootstrap.html is always included on all pages that either rely on bootstrap&amp;rsquo;s CSS, JavaScript or the bootstrap icons.
To minimize bundle size, optional parameters can be passed to the bootstrap partial.
If only the icons are needed, the JavaScript and CSS can be disabled as follows:</description></item><item><title>Tables</title><link>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/table/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mafelp.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-shortcodes/shortcodes/table/</guid><description>Beautify markdown tables</description></item></channel></rss>